<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Haozheng Lin</title>
    <link>https://heizie.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Haozheng Lin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:02:16 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heizie.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[After Work] ESP8266 based information terminal</title>
      <link>https://heizie.github.io/posts/table_terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 16:02:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heizie.github.io/posts/table_terminal/</guid>
      <description>Abstract I&amp;rsquo;ve already built a smart home system based on Home Assistant. The most important task is showing the states of both bathrooms‘ doors because I don’t want to physically check them just like checking other dudes&#39; excretion duration&amp;hellip; And sometimes is just too lazy to take out the phone and check the next bus to the city center, or just too lazy to check the real feel temperature.
There is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instance Segmentation for Application to Deformable Linear Objects</title>
      <link>https://heizie.github.io/posts/masterthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heizie.github.io/posts/masterthesis/</guid>
      <description>Abstract For detecting deformable linear objects (DLO), such as cables, CNN-based methods are insufficient for industrial use, such as for bin-picking tasks. In this paper, based on testing various baseline models from state of the art (s.o.t.a), the reasons for flawless while detecting cables are found and depending on those, we&amp;rsquo;ve developed a combination of a 2 stage vision Transformer with HTC framework (Fig. 1) as an example to reach the best performance of detecting cable with s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image-based tracking of instruments of a laparoscopic manipulator system</title>
      <link>https://heizie.github.io/posts/semesterarbeit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heizie.github.io/posts/semesterarbeit/</guid>
      <description>Abstract For avoiding collision while operating with articulate laparoscopic manipulator system, the position of the instruments should be provided in real-time. Our proposed method provides a reasonable solution for instrument tracking in vivo.   What, How, Results What  A CNN (moded U-Net) based for detecting medical instruments in vivo using binary distribution and gaussian distribution as the label (Fig. 1)         Fig.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
